tds.net 2014-12-17

# TDS Privacy Policy Excerpt - TDS Telecom

Effective Date: September 6, 2012

TDS Telecommunications Corporation ("TDS Telecom"), and its Affiliates; One Neck IT Services Corporation, Vital Support Systems, LLC, TEAM Technologies, LLC, and VISI, Inc. (TDS Hosted and Managed Services, LLC or "TDS HMS") are dedicated to providing superior customer satisfaction and are committed to protecting customer privacy. Both TDS Telecom and TDS HMS (together referred to as "TDS" for the purposes of this policy) take this responsibility seriously as a key component to earning and maintaining our customers' trust.

## Scope

This overview provides highlights of the full TDS Privacy Statement ("Privacy Statement"). This Privacy Statement applies to TDS and any Third Party with whom we share or collect Confidential Personal Information. Third Party refers to agents, vendors, suppliers, subcontractors, and independent contractors. Confidential Personal Information is information that relates to you and identifies or can be used to identify you. This information includes your name, billing address, social security number, driver's license number, credit card number, bank account number, email address, and credit information. By subscribing to our services or accessing our Web sites, you agree to our collection and use of your information as described in the Privacy Statement as may be amended from time to time.

## Collection of your Confidential Personal Information

TDS may collect Confidential Personal Information about you for those purposes specified in this Privacy Statement, or as otherwise permitted by law.

When you visit a TDS Web site, we automatically collect certain information such as your domain type, your IP address, and clickstream information to gauge the effectiveness of our Web sites, improve our online operations, enhance your online experience with customized content, and focus our marketing efforts to better meet the needs of our customers. 

We may store small data files known as cookies, or other technologies, on your computer or mobile browser when you visit certain Web sites. You can disable cookies. However, if you do so your experience on that Web site may be limited.

Additional Details

## Use of your Confidential Personal Information

We may use your Confidential Personal Information to provide you with and manage the services you request, communicate with you to maintain good customer relations or to suggest new products and services that may be of interest to you, conduct industry or consumer surveys, manage, improve and troubleshoot our network and services, enforce our Terms of Service, or for any purpose otherwise permitted or required by law.

Additional Details

## Sharing of your Confidential Personal Information

We will not disclose your Confidential Personal Information without your express or implied consent outside of TDS, its Affiliates, or its authorized agents other than as described in this Privacy Statement. Affiliates refers to any of the Telephone and Data Systems, Inc. owned companies.

TDS may share Confidential Personal Information for purposes permitted by law without your consent such as to help initiate, render, bill, and collect for its products and services.

TDS does not sell your Confidential Personal Information to Third Parties for any purpose other than to enforce our rights under the Terms of Service or as expressly stated in this Privacy Statement.

Additional Details

## Accessing your Confidential Personal Information

Customers who wish to review and/or edit their Confidential Personal Information may do so by contacting us at the number provided on their billing statement.

If you or your Authorized User contacts us via phone, you will be asked to provide your name, the Personal Identification Number ("PIN") (if the account is PIN protected; otherwise you will be asked to provide other information for the purposes of identity verification), and the billing address zip code before we are able to assist you. You or your Authorized user will be asked to present a valid photo ID when requesting account information while at a business office.

Additional Details

## Communication Preferences

If you do not want TDS to use your Confidential Personal Information to contact you for marketing or solicitation purposes (excluding notices about your existing account), TDS Telecom customers may make this request to webcontact@tdstelecom.com, and TDS HMS customers may make this request to events@visi.com. Both TDS Telecom and TDS HMS customers may also make this request to TDS Telecom, Attn: Legal Dept., 525 Junction Road, Madison, Wisconsin 53717.

Additional Details

## Security of your Confidential Personal Information

TDS takes reasonable security safeguards to protect against such risks as loss or unauthorized access, destruction, use, modification, or disclosure of Confidential Personal Information.

Additional Details

## Customer Proprietary Network Information ("CPNI")*

CPNI refers to and includes information that we have about you by virtue of our relationship with you as your service provider. This includes information about your account usage - such as the type and quantity of the services you subscribe to. Use of CPNI is subject to federal laws and regulations with which TDS is required to comply.

When you become a customer of TDS and no later than every two years thereafter, we will send you a notice in the mail explaining your rights concerning Customer Proprietary Network Information ("CPNI Notice").

*Note this section applicable to TDS Telecom customers only

Additional Details

## Contacting Us

TDS welcomes your comments regarding this Privacy Statement. If you have questions about this Privacy Statement or believe that we have not adhered to it, please contact us by writing to us at the following address:

TDS Telecom  
Attn: Legal Dept.  
525 Junction Road  
Madison, WI 53717
